sabreakingnews.co.za 2014-12-12

# Privacy Policy | SA Breaking News

Last updated: 14 November 2012

**1\. GENERAL**

1.1.Incredibility (PTY) LTD (“we” or “us” or “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

1.2.This privacy policy (together with our terms and conditions) sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be used, stored and processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.

**2\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

****2.1.We may collect and process the following information about you:

2.1.1. Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website located at www.sabreakingnews.com or www.sabreakingnews.co.za (“Website”). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website (where relevant), subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services and/or information. We may also ask you for information when you enter a competition or promotion and when you report a problem with the Website.

2.1.2. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

2.1.3. We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

2.1.4. Details of your visits to the Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own purposes or otherwise and the resources (content) that you access.

**3\. IP ADDRESSES**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP (Internet Protocol) address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**4\. COOKIES**

4.1.Our Website uses Cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Website. “Cookies” are small text files transferred by a web server to your hard drive and thereafter stored on your computer. The types of information a Cookie collects include the date and time you visited the Website, your browsing history, your preferences, and your username (where relevant).

4.2.In some instances, our third-party service providers may use Cookies on the Website. We cannot control or access Cookies used by third party service providers. This Privacy Policy covers only Cookies used by us, and not any Cookies used by third parties.

4.3.Cookies enable us to:

4.3.1. estimate our Website’s audience size and usage pattern;

4.3.2. store information about your preferences, which allows us to customize the Website according to your individual interests;

4.3.3. speed up your searches; and

4.3.4. recognise you when you return to the Website.

4.3.5. You have the ability to either accept or decline the use of Cookies on your computer, whether you are registered with us or not. Typically, you can configure your browser to not accept Cookies. However, declining the use of Cookies may limit your access to certain features of the Website.

**5\. STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

5.1.We will do our best to protect your Personal Information, and we will use technology that will help us to do this, however, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of your information to our Website is entirely at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

5.2.Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping that password confidential. Please do not share your password with anyone.

5.3.As we operate the Website from South Africa, all the information, including any personal information we collect or that you submit to us will be stored and processed in South Africa.

5.4.We will keep your personal information only for a reasonable time to enable us to use it for the purposes described in this privacy policy.

**6\. USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

6.1.We use information held about you in the following ways:

6.1.1. To ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 6.1.2. To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

6.1.3. To allow you to participate in interactive features made available on the Website, when you choose to do so.

6.1.4. To notify you about changes to our Website.

6.1.5. We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you

6.1.6. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

6.1.7. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers

reach the kind of audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal information we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

**7\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

7.1.We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in the Companies Act No. 71 of 2008.

7.2.We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

7.2.1. in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

7.2.2. if Incredibility (PTY) LTD or substantially all of its users and/or assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and

7.2.3. if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions

**8\. YOUR RIGHTS**

8.1.You have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.

8.2.Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the Websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these Websites, please note that these Websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal information to these Websites.

**9\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

**10\. GOVERNING LAW**

The contents of this privacy policy shall be governed by South African Law.

**11\. CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed. Contact details are available on our website.
